Erwin Chargaff Papers 1929-1992 Mss.B.C37
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1931-1992; 30 linear feet
  - Carter, Herbert E., 1943-1954, 1957 (Box 15)
    See also Ser.I, National Academy of Sciences
    See also Ser.I, National Research Council
    See also Ser.I, National Science Foundation
    See also Ser.I, Woolley, D.W.
  - Carter, Richard B., 1970 (Box 15)
  - Fred S. Carver, Inc., 1947 (Box 15)
  - Casler, Erika, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Cassuto, A., 1967 (Box 15)
  - Cassuto, Era, 1967-1970 (Box 15)
  - Castaneda, M. Ruiz, 1945 (Box 15)
  - Cataphote Corporation, 1954 (Box 15)
  - Catchpole, Hubert R., 1980 (Box 15)
  - Catherwood, Paul D., 1971 (Box 15)
  - Cattell, Jaques (Box 15)
    See Ser.I, American Men of Science
    See Ser.I, Science
  - Cavalieri, Barbara, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Cavalieri, Liebe F., 1967-1985 (Box 15)
    Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences
    See also Ser.I, Center for Responsible Technology
    See also Ser.I, Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences
  - Center for Responsible Technology, 1983 (Box 15)
    Cavalieri, Liebe F.
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1963 (Box 15)
  - Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique, 1947-1948 (Box 15)
  - Chad, S.R., 1978 (Box 15)
  - Chagas, Carlos, 1962 (Box 15)
  - Chain, E., 1949-1950 (Box 15)
  - Chaix, R., 1952 (Box 15)
  - Chalfan, David, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Chambers, Jack A., 1960, 1964, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Chambers, Leslie A., 1944 (Box 15)
  - Chambers, Robert, 1947 (Box 15)
  - Chambers, Robin, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Chambers, Zoya, 1950 (Box 15)
  - Chan, Lai-Man, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Chandler, Bruce F., 1978 (Box 15)
  - Chang, Mike S.H., 1974 (Box 15)
  - Chang, Sing-Hsiung, 1971-1974 (Box 15)
  - Chantrenne, H., 1964 (Box 15)
  - Chanutin, Alfred, 1948, 1954 (Box 15)
  - Chao, Fu-Chuan, 1955-1956 (Box 15)
  - Chase, Allan, 1964-1980 (Box 15)
  - Chatterjee, A.K., 1964 (Box 15)
  - Chemical Abstracts, 1948-1956, 1963 (Box 15)
  - Chemical and Engineering News, 1951, 1977-1983 (Box 15)
  - Chemical Process Company, 1949 (Box 15)
  - Chemical Rubber Company, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Chemical Society, 1951-1959, 1971-1975 (Box 15)
  - Chemische Gesellschaft Zürich, 1949 (Box 15)
  - Chen, John H., 1968 (Box 15)
  - Chen, Kou-Ching, 1964 (Box 15)
  - Chen, Ming Sheng, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Cheong, Loretta Chiuh-Yeou, 1965-1977 (Box 15)
  - Chernesky, Ed, [198-?] (Box 15)
  - Chernuchin, Paul, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Chester County Mushroom Laboratories, 1955 (Box 15)
  - Chevallier, Paul, 1948 (Box 15)
  - Chimia, 1976 (Box 15)
    Nitschmann, Hans
  - Chin, Edward B.F., Jr., 1968-1972 (Box 15)
  - Chinard, Francis P., 1973 (Box 15)
  - Chirigos, Michael A., 1972 (Box 15)
  - Chmiel, Józef, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Cho, Dong Hyun, 1963 (Box 16)
  - Chowdhury, Subrata, 1973 (Box 16)
  - Christensen, Gerald M., 1976 (Box 16)
  - Christy, Nicholas P., 1978 (Box 16)
  - Chuvikov, Pavel, 1961 (Box 16)
  - Ciba Pharmaceutical Products, Inc., 1947-1951 (Box 16)
  - Ciencia Y Desarrollo, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Cinader, B., 1954 (Box 16)
  - Citizens Against Toxic Sprays, Inc., 1976 (Box 16)
  - Claman, Henry N., 1980 (Box 16)
  - Clamp, J.R., 1962 (Box 16)
  - Clark, F.M., 1946-1947 (Box 16)
  - Clark, Irwin, 1964-1965, 1971 (Box 16)
  - Clark, Wilson, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Clarke, Donald D., [196-] (Box 16)
  - Clarke, Hans Thacher, 1942-1965, 1973 (Box 16)
  - Claude, Albert, 1943 (Box 16)
  - Clay-Adams Company, Inc., 1954 (Box 16)
  - Clayton, Roderick K., 1961-1962 (Box 16)
  - Clinical Pediatrics, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Clouet, Doris H., [196-] (Box 16)
  - Cmelik, S., 1951-1952 (Box 16)
  - Cobb, R., 1947 (Box 16)
  - Codington, John F., 1955 (Box 16)
  - Cody, Sherwin, 1948 (Box 16)
  - Coghill, Robert D., 1946 (Box 16)
  - Cohen, Bertram I., 1970 (Box 16)
  - Cohen, Gerald, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Cohen, Georges N., 1947 (Box 16)
    See also Ser.I, Congrès International de
  - Cohen, Philip Pacy, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Cohen, Jack S., 1973 (Box 16)
  - Cohen, Seymour S., 1942-1982 (Box 16)
  - Cohen, Stanley N., 1977 (Box 16)
  - Cohen-Boulakia, Fabien (Box 16)
    See Ser.I, Boulakia, Fabien Cohen
  - Cohn, Edwin J., 1942-1949 (Box 16)
    See also Ser.I, Edsall, John T.
    See also Ser.I, United States Public Health Service
  - Cohn, Waldo E. (Box 16)
    American Chemical Society
    Benesch, Ruth E., 1980
    Livingston, H.K., 1968
    National Research Council
    Petersen, George B.
    Seegers, Walter Henry, 1976, 1980
    Sinsheimer, Robert L., 1968
    Smellie, R.M.S., 1972
    See also Ser.I, American Institute of Biological Sciences
    See also Ser.I, Bransome, Edwin D., Jr.
    See also Ser.I, Hodes, Marion Edward
    See also Ser.I, Livingston, H.K.
    See also Ser.I, National Academy of Sciences. Office of Biochemical Nomenclature
    - Folder #1, 1950-1955 (Box 16)
    - Folder #2, 1956-1966 (Box 16)
    - Folder #3, 1967-1980 (Box 16)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory of Quantitative Biology, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Cole, Leonard A., 1979 (Box 16)
  - Collège de France, 1964-1965 (Box 17)
    Roche, Jean
    See also Ser.VI, Collège de France
  - College of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey, 1974 (Box 17)
  - College Science Improvement Project, 1970 (Box 17)
  - Collier, H.B., 1948 (Box 17)
  - Collier, J.R., 1959-1960 (Box 17)
  - Colobert, L., 1964 (Box 17)
  - Colover, J., 1957 (Box 17)
  - Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center, 1960, 1962 (Box 17)
  - Columbia University, 1941-1989; 10 folders (Box 17)
    Business; Cancer, chemotherapy; Columbia University; Committee activities; Conferences and symposia; Cytogenetics; Educational matters; Laboratory techniques, equipment; World War II -- Impact on science
    - Folder #1, 1941-1944 (Box 17)
    - Folder #2, 1945-1948 (Box 17)
    - Folder #3, 1949-1953 (Box 17)
    - Folder #4, 1954-1957 (Box 17)
    - Folder #5, 1958-1960 (Box 17)
    - Folder #6, 1961-1964 (Box 17)
    - Folder #7, 1965-1966 (Box 18)
    - Folder #8, 1967-1969 (Box 18)
    - Folder #9, 1970-1972 (Box 18)
    - Folder #10, 1973-1989 (Box 18)
  - Columbia University. Forum, 1964-1975 (Box 18)
    Ambrose, Lee
  - Columbia University. Health Sciences Library, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Columbia University. Institute for the Study of Science in Human Affairs, 1968-1970 (Box 18)
    Truman, David B.
  - Columbia University. Jesup Lectures, 1958-1959 (Box 18)
  - Columbia University Press, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Columbia University. Teachers College, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Columbian Carbon Company, 1949-1951 (Box 18)
  - Commercial Solvents Corporation, 1950 (Box 18)
  - Committee for Survival, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Committee on Science and Freedom, 1958 (Box 18)
  - Committee to Defend the Conspiracy, 1969 (Box 18)
    Braverman, Albert S.
  - Commoner, Barry, 1962 (Box 18)
    See also Ser.I, Davidson, J. Norman,
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1965-1967, 1974 (Box 18)
    See also Ser.I, Rittenberg, David
  - The Company of Biologists Limited, 1961 (Box 18)
  - Comparative Biochemistry and Physiology, 1958-1962 (Box 18)
  - Conacyt, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Concord Laboratories, 1950 (Box 19)
  - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils, 1951-1952, 1958 (Box 19)
  - Conference on Personal Freedom in an Era of Social Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Congrès International de Biochimie, 1951-1954 (Box 19)
    Cohen, Georges N.
  - Connelly, Edward, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Connors, Catherine, 1965-1975 (Box 19)
    Gambino-Giuffrida, Angela
  - Conway, Brian E., 1955 (Box 19)
  - Cooper, William G., 1961 (Box 19)
  - Copenhagen University, 1961 (Box 19)
  - Corcoran, A.C., 1945 (Box 19)
  - Cori, Carl F., 1957, 1965 (Box 19)
    Kamen, Martin
  - Cori, Gerty T., 1945, 1954, 1957 (Box 19)
  - Corn Products Refining Co., 1946-1949, 1957 (Box 19)
  - Cornatzer, W.E., 1965 (Box 19)
  - Cornell University, 1964-1966 (Box 19)
  - Cornell University Press, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Corning Glass Works, 1956 (Box 19)
  - Cornwell, W.S., 1971 (Box 19)
  - Corpe, William A., 1959 (Box 19)
  - Corwin, Harry O., 1972 (Box 19)
  - Cosín García, Jesús, 1947 (Box 19)
  - Council for the Advancement of Negroes in Science, 1959 (Box 19)
  - Council of Europe, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Cournand, Andrea, 1973 (Box 19)
  - Courtois, Jean Émile, 1964-1965 (Box 19)
    See also Ser.I, Charles Leopold Mayer Prize
    See also Ser.I, Société de Chimie Biologique
  - Cowie, Dean B., 1956 (Box 19)
  - Cowles, Philip B., 1955 (Box 19)
  - Cox, E.C., 1959 (Box 19)
  - Cox, H.R., 1943-1945 (Box 19)
  - Craig, Lyman C., 1965 (Box 19)
  - Crampton, Charles Freeman, 1950-1961 (Box 19)
    See also Ser.I, Lipshitz, Rakoma
    See also Ser.I, National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis
  - Crane, William E., 1951 (Box 19)
  - Creedmor Institute for Psychobiologic Studies, 1951 (Box 19)
  - Crick, Francis H.C., 1954, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Crosbie, George W. (Box 19)
    See Ser.I, Davidson, J. Norman
  - Crouch, Robert J., 1981 (Box 19)
    Dirksen, Marie-Luise
    Stavrianopoulos, Yiannis G.
  - Croxatto, H., 1945-1948 (Box 19)
  - Cuatrecasas, Pedro, 1978-1982 (Box 19)
  - Cullis, Tara (Box 19)
    See Ser.I, Suzuki, David T.
  - Curtis, Howard J., 1954 (Box 19)
  - Cushing, John, 1961 (Box 19)
  - Cyriax, Bernhard, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Czerlinski, George H., 1971 (Box 19)
  - Daetsch, Willard Ticknor, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Dahl, Lars-Gösta, 1949 (Box 19)
  - Dall'Asta, Eberhard R., 1970 (Box 19)
  - Dam, Henrik, 1943-1949 (Box 19)
  - Damon Runyan Memorial Fund, 1950, 1957 (Box 19)
    See also Ser.IIa, Damon Runyan Memorial
  - Danishefsky, Isidore, [196-] (Box 19)
  - Dannenberg, Arthur M., Jr., 1951 (Box 19)
  - Danon, Arlette, 1962-1964 (Box 19)
    See also Ser.I, McEntee, Catherine
  - Daoust, Roger, 1951 (Box 19)
  - Darco Corporation, 1946 (Box 19)
  - Darnell, James E., Jr., 1971 (Box 19)
  - Das Gupta, N.N., 1966 (Box 19)
  - Dashman, Theodore, 1957-1964 (Box 19)
  - Da Silva, Alberto Carvalho, 1947 (Box 19)
  - Datta, Prasanta K., 1960 (Box 19)
  - Datta, Ranajit Kumar, 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - Davenport, Demorest, 1963 (Box 19)
  - Davenport, Horace, 1968 (Box 19)
  - Davidson, J. Norman (Box 20)
    Academic Press, Inc.
    Baddiley, J.
    Brachet, Jean
    Commoner, Barry, 1967
    Crosbie, George W.
    Dounce, Alexander L.
    Glock, Gertrude E.
    Hammarsten, E.
    Hogeboom, George H.
    Hotchkiss, Rollin D.
    Journal of Biological Chemistry
    Kalckar, Herman M.
    Lajtha, L.G.
    Leslie, Ian
    Reichard, Peter
    Schneider, Walter C.
    Smith, J.D.
    Swift, Hewson H.
    Vendrely, R.
    Verkade, P.E.
    Welch, Arnold D.
    See also Ser.I, Baddiley, J.
    See also Ser.I, Biochemical Society
    See also Ser.I, Brown, George
    See also Ser.I, Glock, Gertrude
    See also Ser.I, Holiday, Ensor R.
    See also Ser.I, Jordan, D.O.
    See also Ser.I, Kalckar, Herman
    See also Ser.I, Schlenk, Fritz
    See also Ser.I, Smith, J.D.
    See also Ser.I, Stacey, M.
    See also Ser.I, Welch, Arnold D.
    - Folder #1, 1947-1953 (Box 20)
    - Folder #2, 1953-1956 (Box 20)
    - Folder #3, 1957-1959 (Box 20)
    - Folder #4, 1960-1972 (Box 20)
  - Davie, Earl, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Davies, J.T., 1949 (Box 20)
  - Davies, Martin, 1966 (Box 20)
  - Davies, R.O., 1955 (Box 20)
  - Davison, P.S., 1964 (Box 20)
  - Davydov, Oleg V., 1984 (Box 20)
  - Dawid, I.B., 1958-1960 (Box 20)
  - Dawson, Charles R., 1952 (Box 20)
  - Deatherage, Fred E., 1971 (Box 20)
  - De Barbieri, A., 1956, 1968 (Box 20)
    See also Ser.I, Istituto Sieroterapico
  - deBary, William Theodore, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Debois, Jean M., 1959 (Box 20)
  - Debov, S., 1959 (Box 20)
  - DeBrunner, Ruth, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - De Bruyn, Peter P.H., 1950 (Box 20)
  - De Castro, Firmino T., 1960 (Box 20)
  - Decker, John L., 1958 (Box 20)
  - De Duve, C., 1976 (Box 20)
  - De Franceschi, Antonio, 1949-1966 (Box 20)
  - De Garilhe, M. Privat, 1961 (Box 20)
  - De Lamirande, Gaston, 1952 (Box 20)
  - Dell, Robert A., 1973 (Box 20)
  - Delta Chemical Works, 1951 (Box 20)
  - Dempsey, William S., 1947 (Box 20)
  - DeNike, L. Douglas, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Denkewalter, Robert G., 1970 (Box 20)
  - Dent, Charles E., 1953 (Box 20)
  - De Roberts, E., 1951 (Box 20)
  - Derrick, John B., 1963 (Box 20)
  - Desai, B.M., 1969 (Box 20)
  - Deshpande, V.N., 1969 (Box 20)
  - Desnuelle, P., 1952 (Box 20)
  - Desreux, V., 1949-1952 (Box 20)
  - deStevens, George, 1970-1973 (Box 20)
  - Detroit Institute of Cancer Research, 1951 (Box 21)
  - Deuticke, H.J., 1949 (Box 21)
  - Deutsche Akademie der Naturforscher Leopoldina, 1971, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Devey, James D., 1949 (Box 21)
  - Devons, Samuel, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Dewey, Virginia C., 1954-1955 (Box 21)
  - De Wijs, Hermine Maria, 1960, 1962 (Box 21)
    See also Ser.I, Van Leeuwen, Elisabeth
  - Dhar, N.R., 1942 (Box 21)
  - Dianzani, Mario Umberto, 1950 (Box 21)
  - Di Cyan, Erwin, 1965 (Box 21)
  - Difco Laboratories, 1943, 1950 (Box 21)
  - Di Maiorca, Giampiero, 1957 (Box 21)
  - Dirksen, Marie-Luise (Box 21)
    See Ser.I, Crouch, Robert J.
  - Dische, Irene, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Dische, Zacharias, 1952-1976 (Box 21)
  - Djerassi, Carl, 1954, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Dobrewski, Ywan, 1958 (Box 21)
  - Dochez, A.R., 1942-1943, 1949 (Box 21)
  - Dodington, Peter, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Domherr, Ludwig L., 1958-1961, 1979 (Box 21)
  - Donachie, W.D., 1966 (Box 21)
  - Doniger, Ruth, 1949-1957 (Box 21)
    See also Ser.I, Green, Charlotte
    See also Ser.I, Magasanik, Boris
  - Donner, Ludvik, 1946 (Box 21)
  - Doran Instrument Company, Limited, 1954-1955 (Box 21)
  - Dorfman, Albert, 1955 (Box 21)
  - Dorsey, John M., 1976, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Doty, Paul, 1952-1953, 1966 (Box 21)
  - Doubleday and Company, Inc., 1969, 1973-1975 (Box 21)
  - Dounce, Alexander L., 1952-1955 (Box 21)
  - Dow Chemical Company, 1950-1954, 1961 (Box 21)
  - Dow Corning Corporation, 1952 (Box 21)
  - Dowben, Robert M. (Box 21)
    See Ser.I, Cantor, Charles A.
  - Downs, Cora M., 1952 (Box 21)
  - Doyle, Christine, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Doyle, Diana Q., 1977 (Box 21)
  - Drabkin, David L., 1948 (Box 21)
    See also Ser.I, Annual Reviews, Inc.
  - Drea, William Francis, 1951 (Box 21)
  - Drew, Brian, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Drew University, 1977-1978 (Box 21)
  - Drinker, Cecil K., 1946 (Box 21)
  - D'Souza, Leo, 1965 (Box 21)
  - Dubois, Jacques E., 1955-1956 (Box 21)
  - Dubos, René, 1968, 1976-1977 (Box 21)
    See also Ser.I, Harvey Society
  - Dubrovsky, B., [1976] (Box 21)
  - Duchesne, Jules, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Duggan, Edward L., 1956 (Box 21)
  - Dunn, D.B., 1963 (Box 21)
  - Dunn, John A., 1970 (Box 21)
  - Dunning, John R., 1963-1964 (Box 21)
  - E.I. Du Pont de Nemours and Company, 1961-1962 (Box 21)
  - Duschinsky, R., 1979 (Box 21)
  - Duschnes, Philip C., 1953 (Box 21)
  - Dutta, Sujit Kumar, 1952 (Box 21)
  - Dutton, Herbert J., 1953 (Box 21)
  - Du Vigneaud, Vincent, 1943, 1955, 1965 (Box 21)
  - Dworak, Brigitte, 1969 (Box 21)
  - E-C Apparatus Company, 1954 (Box 21)
  - Eagle, Harry, 1947, 1953, 1956 (Box 21)
    See also Ser.I, Pharmacological Reviews
  - Eagle Signal Company, 1951-1952 (Box 21)
  - Ealing Corporation, 1956, 1972 (Box 21)
  - Eastern Colleges Science Conference, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Eastern Packing Company, Inc., 1942 (Box 21)
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1946-1953, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - Eaton, Virginia, 1946 (Box 21)
  - Eaves, George, 1970 (Box 21)
  - Ebel, J.P., 1963 (Box 21)
  - Ebener, W., 1954 (Box 21)
  - Edelman, Isidore S., 1977-1980 (Box 21)
  - Edelstein, Stuart J., 1980 (Box 21)
  - Editions Gallimard, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Edmonds, Mary, 1957 (Box 21)
  - Edsall, Geoffrey, 1963, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Edsall, John T., 1944-1984 (Box 21)
    United States Public Health Service, 1948
    See also Ser.I, Advances in Protein Chemistry
    See also Ser.I, American Academy of Arts and Sciences
  - Educational Committee to Halt Atomic Weapons Spread, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Efron, Robert, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Egami, Fujio, 1951-1958, 1972, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Eggenberger, David, 1963 (Box 21)
  - Eggman, Luther, 1951 (Box 21)
  - Egneus, Hans, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Egyptian Red Crescent Society, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Ehrenfeld, David W., 1976, 1979 (Box 22)
    Rockefeller University Press
    See also Ser.I, Rockefeller University Press
  - Ehrenpreis, Seymour, 1960 (Box 22)
  - Ehrensvärd, Gösta, 1949-1959 (Box 22)
  - Ehrlich, Gert, 1952 (Box 22)
  - Eigen, Manfred, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Eimer and Amend, 1949 (Box 22)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 22)
    See Ser.I, Society for Social Responsibility
  - Albert Einstein College of Medicine, 1966, 1973, 1976 (Box 22)
    Nathan, Helmuth
  - Eisenberg, Max Aaron, [1963], 1988 (Box 22)
  - Einsenhower, Dwight D. (Box 22)
    See Ser.IIa, Nutrition Foundation, Inc.
  - Eisgrau, Siegfried, 1961, 1963 (Box 22)
  - Elek Micro Analytical Laboratories, 1948-1952 (Box 22)
  - Eliel, Ernest L. (Box 22)
    See Ser.I, Mislow, Kurt
  - Eliot, George, 1954 (Box 22)
  - Elkes, J., 1950 (Box 22)
  - Elliott, K.A.C., 1942 (Box 22)
    See also Ser.I, McGill University
  - Ellman, George L., 1965 (Box 22)
  - Ellouz, Radhouane, 1970-1973 (Box 22)
    Some in French and German
  - Elmendorff, Harald S., 1958 (Box 22)
  - Elsasser, Walter M., 1975-1976 (Box 22)
  - Elsevier Publishing Company, 1951-1978 (Box 22)
    Boelsma, E.
    Saturday Review
    See also Ser.I, Biochimica et Biophysica Acta
    See also Ser.I, Saturday Review
  - Elson, David, 1949-1974 (Box 22)
    Bloch, Emmy
    See also Ser.I, Franzl, Robert E.
    See also Ser.I, Kream, Jacob
  - Emberson, W., 1980 (Box 22)
  - Emerson, Sterling, 1958 (Box 22)
  - Enciclopedia del Novecento, 1972-1973 (Box 22)
  - Encyclopedia Americana, 1966 (Box 22)
  - Engel, Lewis L., 1976 (Box 22)
  - Engelhardt, W.A., 1963 (Box 22)
  - Engström, Arne, 1947 (Box 22)
  - Enzyme Club, 1955-1975 (Box 22)
    Siekevitz, Philip
  - Ephrussi, Boris, 1957-1965; 10.0 Item(s) (Box 22)
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- National Academy of Sciences; Cytogenetics; Honors -- Nobel Prize; Reviews
  - Eppstein, Samuel, 1971 (Box 22)
  - Epstein, Emanuel, 1976 (Box 22)
  - Ercoli, N., 1950-1951 (Box 22)
  - Ergle, David R., 1958 (Box 22)
  - Erlanger, Bernard F., 1967 (Box 22)
    See also Ser.I, Neurath, Hans
  - Errera, Maurice, 1952 (Box 22)
  - Espejo, Miguel, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Esso Standard Oil Company, 1953 (Box 22)
  - Eston, Charlotte, 1962 (Box 22)
  - Ethyl Corporation, 1951 (Box 22)
  - Etzioni, Amitai, 1972 (Box 22)
  - Euell, Julian T., 1976 (Box 22)
  - European Journal of Biochemistry, 1967 (Box 22)
  - European Parliament, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Evans, Earl A., Jr., 1945-1965 (Box 22)
  - Evans, W. Charles, 1943 (Box 22)
  - W.G. Evans and Sons, Ltd., 1953 (Box 22)
  - Evans Biological Institute, 1943 (Box 22)
  - Ewald, Paul P., 1968 (Box 23)
  - Ewing, Maurice, 1961 (Box 23)
  - Excerpta Medica, 1950 (Box 23)
  - Experientia, 1949-1979 (Box 23)
    Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc.
    Mislin, Hans
  - Experimental Cell Research, 1949-1966 (Box 23)
    Ehrensvärd, Gösta
    Mazia, Daniel
    Reio, Vera
  - Ezell, George H., 1983 (Box 23)
  - Faber, Mogens, 1947-1951, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Fabre, René, 1951-1955 (Box 23)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson University, 1976, 1982 (Box 23)
  - Faltsis, Sotiris G., 1974-1979 (Box 23)
  - Faraday Society, 1949-1958 (Box 23)
    Butler, J.A.V.
    Frazer, A.C.
    Peacocke, A.R.
  - Farber, Florence Eileen (Box 23)
    - Folder #1, 1964-1972 (Box 23)
    - Folder #2, 1973-1981 (Box 23)
  - Farkas, Daniel L., 1978 (Box 23)
  - Farley, David L., 1945 (Box 23)
  - Faulkner, Robert D., 1972 (Box 23)
  - Feazel, C.E., 1951 (Box 23)
  - Federation of American Scientists, 1955, 1961 (Box 23)
  - Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology, 1951-1981 (Box 23)
  - Feigelson, Philip, 1961-1975 (Box 23)
    See also Ser.I, New York Academy of
  - Feigl, Fritz, 1951, 1959 (Box 23)
  - Feiguinson, N.I., 1964 (Box 23)
  - Feinberg, Deborah, 1977 (Box 23)
  - Feinberg, Gerald, 1976, 1980 (Box 23)
  - Ferreira, Ricardo, 1980 (Box 23)
  - Feissly, R., 1946-1955 (Box 23)
  - Feith, P.R., 1965 (Box 23)
    Moreau, Jean
    See also Ser.I, H.P. Heineken Prize
  - Feldman, Joseph D., 1968 (Box 23)
  - Felix, A., 1943 (Box 23)
  - Felix, Kurt, 1956 (Box 23)
  - Felsenfeld, Gary, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Felton, Robert, 1946 (Box 23)
  - Ferger, Martha F., 1949 (Box 23)
    Vischer, Ernst Benedikt
  - Ferguson, John H., 1944-1947 (Box 23)
  - Ferreira, Ricardo, 1968, 1971 (Box 23)
  - Ferriman, D., 1952 (Box 23)
  - Ferry, Ronald M., 1968 (Box 23)
  - Fiedler, Henry George, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Fieser, Louis F., 1954 (Box 23)
  - Fieser, Mary, 1953-1954 (Box 23)
  - Figdor, Hans G., 1965 (Box 23)
  - Filipowicz, Bronislaw, 1957 (Box 23)
  - Finamore, F.J., 1963-1964 (Box 23)
    Volkin, Elliot
  - Fine Organics, Inc., 1944-1949 (Box 23)
  - Finean, J.B., 1951 (Box 23)
  - Finnish Academy of Sciences, 1955 (Box 23)
  - Finnish Chemical Society, 1960 (Box 23)
  - Firshein, William, 1958 (Box 23)
  - Fischel, E.E., 1945 (Box 23)
  - Fischer, Hermann O.L., 1945-1955 (Box 23)
  - Fisher Scientific Company, 1952-1956, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Fittko, Elisabeth, 1960 (Box 24)
    See also Ser.I, Ekstein, Hans
  - Fitzgerald, Patricia Lee, 1951-1952, 1962 (Box 24)
  - Fitzgerald, Patrick J., 1958 (Box 24)
  - Flamm, W. Gary, 1968 (Box 24)
  - Fleischer, Sidney, 1961-1962 (Box 24)
  - Fleischhacker, Desider, 1951 (Box 24)
  - Fleischhacker, M., 1973 (Box 24)
  - Fleischmann Laboratories, 1943-1946, 1953 (Box 24)
    Frey, Charles N.
  - Fleming, Donald, 1969 (Box 24)
  - Fletcher, Dean C., 1963 (Box 24)
  - Fletcher, Hewitt G., Jr., 1946-1950 (Box 24)
  - Fleury, Paul, 1952, 1954 (Box 24)
  - Flodin, N.W., 1953 (Box 24)
  - Flood, Frank P., 1943 (Box 24)
  - Florida State University, 1963-1965 (Box 24)
  - Flowers, H.M., 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Folch-Pi, Jordi, 1941-1977 (Box 24)
  - Foltin, Helen, 1962 (Box 24)
  - Fondation Pour la Recherche Scientifique sur le Cancer, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Font Rios, Cecilio, 1981 (Box 24)
  - Ford, Joseph M., [1978], 1980, 1982 (Box 24)
  - Henry Ford Hospital, 1959 (Box 24)
  - Fordham University, 1960-1962, 1981 (Box 24)
  - Forman, Paul, 1979 (Box 24)
  - Formijne, P., 1947 (Box 24)
  - Forrest, Irene S., 1958, 1974-1975 (Box 24)
  - Forsdyke, Donald R., 1980 (Box 24)
  - Fortune, 1948, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Foster, Allan B., 1953-1954 (Box 24)
  - Foster, G.L., 1949, 1958 (Box 24)
  - Foster, R.H.K., 1942, 1947 (Box 24)
  - Foundation for Advanced Education in the Sciences, Inc., 1981 (Box 24)
  - Fowler, Dorothy I., 1950 (Box 24)
  - Fox, Charles C., Jr., 1963 (Box 24)
  - Fox, Sidney W., 1964, 1971 (Box 24)
    See also Ser.I, American Chemical Society Monographs
    See also Ser.I, Florida State University
    See also Ser.I, International Symposium on the Origin of Life
  - Fraenkel-Conrat, Heinz, 1964-1978 (Box 24)
    See also Ser.I, American Association for
  - Frajola, Walter J., 1953 (Box 24)
  - Franco, Stella, 1971-1974, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Frank, Leonard, 1980 (Box 24)
  - Frank, Sylvia, 1954-1955 (Box 24)
  - Franklin, Edward C., 1946 (Box 24)
  - Franklin, R.E., 1954 (Box 24)
  - Franzl, Robert E., 1949-1954 (Box 24)
    Faber, Mogens
    Kurnick, N.B.
    See also Ser.I, Hickrill Chemical Research Foundation, Inc.
    See also Ser.I, Kurnick, N.B.
  - Fratelli Fabbri Editori, 1968 (Box 24)
  - Frazer, Alastair C., 1946-1958, 1964 (Box 24)
    Viobin Corporation
    See also Ser.I, Sperry, Warren M.
  - Fredericq, E., 1964 (Box 24)
  - Freeman, Brian, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Freeman, William H., 1968 (Box 24)
  - Freifelder, David, 1965 (Box 24)
  - French, C.S., 1947, 1960 (Box 24)
  - French, Dexter, [196-] (Box 24)
  - Fresco, Jacques R., 1962 (Box 24)
  - Frey-Wyssling, A., 1951 (Box 24)
  - Frick, Paul G., 1950 (Box 24)
  - Fridovich, Irwin, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Fried, Seraphine, 1945 (Box 24)
  - Friedheim, Ernst A.H., 1946, 1971-1972 (Box 24)
  - Friedkin, Morris E., 1954 (Box 24)